Charles Mingus Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Business Papers (Box 54-64)
  - Debut Records, Inc.
    - Correspondence Sent: Corporate (Box-folder 57/17)
      - A & I Record Distributors
        - Lovette, Harol E.
      - Al Smith's Record Bar
        - Mingus, Charles
      - All Star Theatrical Agency
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Allied Record Sales
        - Mingus, Charles
      - American Jazz Annual
        - Mingus, Celia
      - American Mercantile Company
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Ann's Record Mart
        - Eagle, Kiriki
      - Associated Booking Corp.
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Atlantic Records Corporation
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Billboard Publishing Co.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Book Clearing House, Inc.
        - Eagle, Kiriki
      - Bureau of Motor Vehicles
        - Mingus, Lucille [Celia]
      - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank
        - Debut Records
      - Columbia Music Company
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Coastal Recording Co., Inc.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - College Music Distributing Co.
        - Brandt, William J.
      - Columbia Music Co.
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Commercial Controls Corp. (Box-folder 57/17)
        - Hall, LeRoy P.
      - D & D Distributing
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Daniel Wright Record Shop
        - Brandt, William
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Decca Records
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Edward R. White, Inc.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - F & F Enrterprises
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Florida Record and Appliance Company (Florida Record and Music Co.)
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Fortesque Jazz Club
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Galveston Negro Chamber of Commerce
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Gray Manufacturing Co.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Har-Bock Music Co.
        - Bock, Richard
      - Harper's Magazine
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Henry C. Knoblauch & Son
        - Ferris, M.
      - Interstate Phonograph Corp.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Jan and Mike Record Shop
        - Ferris, M.
      - Jawood L. Anderson, Inc.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Jazz Hot
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Jazz Monthly
        - Mingus, Celia
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Jazz Promotion, Inc.
        - Ferris, M.
      - Ken Paulsen Associates
        - Dorr-Dorynek, Diane
      - KFMB Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - KFRE - California Inland Broadcasting Co.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - KLAC Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - KLUF Radio - "Music with Maggie"
        - Ferris, M
      - KNBC Radio (Box-folder 57/17)
        - Mingus, Charles
      - KUTA Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Lighthouse Cafe
        - Brandt, William
      - Lowenstein's
        - Eagle, Kiriki
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Mademoiselle Magazine (Box-folder 57/18)
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Mangold Distributing Co.
        - Brandt, William
      - Marnell Distributing Co.
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Meade Music House
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Melody Sales Co.
        - Brandt, William
      - Microfusion, Inc.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Microphone Music
        - Brandt, William
      - The Modern Jazz Club
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Monroe Music Co.
        - Ferris, M.
      - Morris Distributing Co.
        - Brandt, William
      - Motor Freight Director
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Music Barn
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Music-Please Co.
        - Ferris, M.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Music Suppliers of New England, Inc.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Nelson Music House
        - Ferris, M
      - New York State Department of Labor
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Norfolk Virginian-Pilot
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Pan American Record Supply Co.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Portem Distributing
        - Debut Records [no individual specified]
      - Railway Express Agency
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Rave Recording and Distributing Co.
        - Mingus, Celia
      - The Record Shop (Box-folder 57/18)
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Seven Arts Book Society
        - Mingus, Celia
      - State University of New York College for Teachers
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Tempo
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Trans-Disc Corporation
        - Lovette, harold E.
      - Transition
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Tri-State Record Distributors, Inc.
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Tru-Tone Distributing
        - Eagle, Kiriki
        - Mingus, Celia
      - Voice of America
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WAAF Radio
        - Mingus, Celia
      - WCAM Bureau of Broadcasting
        - Lovette, Harold E.
      - WERE Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WFAH Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WJQS Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WNEW Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WNJR Radio
        - Mingus, Charles
      - WOR Radio
        - Ferris, M.
      - WPEO Radio
        - Ferris, M.
      - WQBC Delta Broadcasting Co.
        - Mingus, Charles
    - Correspondence Sent: Individuals (Box-folder 57/19)
      - Anderson, Eric
      - Arseneault, Jack
      - Bailey, Franklin
      - Berendt, Joachim E.
      - Bergman, Cadet G.T.
      - Bernard, Naomi
      - Brautigam, Anders
      - Carroll, Harold F.
      - Cholinski, Henryk Z.
      - Coluzzi, Nelson
      - Conover, Willis
      - Dale, Brian
      - Dennis, John (Box-folder 57/19)
      - Díaz, Frank, Jr.
      - Divok, Joe
      - Fleiss, Marcel
      - Fiorito, Edward
      - Gannon, Bob
      - Gauguin, Jam
      - Givens, Spaulding
      - Gleason, Ralph J.
      - Groff, James
      - Henderson, Robert P.
      - Henninger, Fred A.
      - Hughes, Langston
      - Kantor, Frederick I.
      - Kirkwood, J.
      - Larmay, Lou
      - Lawson, Kathy
      - Lengsfelder, H.F.
      - Lerman, N.D.
      - Levister, Alonzo
      - Lomoe, Wallace
      - Lovette, Harold E.
      - Manning, Don
      - McCoy, Sid
      - Mingo, Leonard
      - Morgan, Alun
      - Nelson, Beatrice
      - Norvo, Red and Eve
      - O'Brien, Neil C.
      - O'Connor, Father Norman J.
      - Parker, Chan
      - Purlongo, Bob
      - Raeburn, Boyd
      - Rappoport, Jon
      - Roach, Max
      - Rubins, Helen
      - Seilagy, Bob
      - Sewell, John W.
      - Shaffer, Dr. J.R.
      - Simon, George
      - Slocum, Beverly
      - Smith, F.T.
      - Soucie, Gary A.
      - Stoopack, Irving
      - Summarrisse, Bob
      - Ulanov, Barry
      - Waldorf, O.D.
      - Watton, Dick
      - Westberg, Nils
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 57/20)
    - General Services: Vender Sales and Services
      - Banking:
        - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank
          - Cancelled checks (Box-folder 58/1-2)
          - Charges to account (Box-folder 58/3)
          - Deposit receipts (Box-folder 58/4)
          - Statements (Box-folder 58/5)
          - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Publicity [publications]
        - Down Beat Magazine (Box-folder 58/7)
        - Long Player Publications Ltd. (Box-folder 58/8)
        - Metronome Magazine (Box-folder 58/9)
      - Record Sales and Related Services
        - ABC Distributing Corporation (Box-folder 58/10)
        - A.M. Zimmermann & Co. (Box-folder 58/11)
        - Aetna Photoengraving Co., Inc. (Box-folder 58/12)
        - Albert Schultz, inc. (Box-folder 58/13)
        - Amsa Arts Ménagers (Box-folder 58/14)
        - Artype Press, Inc. (Box-folder 58/15)
        - Audio-Video Recording Co. (Box-folder 58/16)
        - Bill Spilka (Box-folder 58/17)
        - Cardinal Export Corp. (Box-folder 58/18)
        - Center Records (Box-folder 58/19)
        - Chatton Distributing Co. (Box-folder 58/20)
        - Commercial Music Co., Inc. (Box-folder 58/21)
        - Contemporary Distributing Co. (Box-folder 58/22)
        - Departmaent of the Army and the Air Force (Box-folder 58/23)
        - Dexter Distributing (Box-folder 58/24)
        - Elite Record Company of Canada (Box-folder 58/25)
        - EMCO Distributors (Box-folder 58/26)
        - Empire Record Corporation (Box-folder 59/1-2)
        - Equitable Stationery Company (Box-folder 59/3)
        - Erpol Music Ltd. (Box-folder 59/4)
        - Esoteric Recording Services (Box-folder 59/5)
        - Gem Albums (Box-folder 59/6)
        - Gimbel Brothers, Inc. (Box-folder 59/7)
        - Japan Sales Co. Ltd. (Box-folder 59/8)
        - Jazz Box (Box-folder 59/9)
        - Kaltman Press, Inc. (Box-folder 59/10)
        - Lone Star Records (Box-folder 59/11)
        - Milton Phono Records Co. (Box-folder 59/12)
        - Morris Distributing Co. (Box-folder 59/13)
        - Peerless Album Co. (Box-folder 59/14)
        - RCA Victor Division: Radio Corporation of America (Box-folder 59/15)
        - Record Sales Co. (Box-folder 59/16)
        - S. Posner Sons Paper and Packaging Products (Box-folder 59/17)
        - Samuel R. Rosenbaum (Box-folder 59/18)
        - Shelley Products Ltd. (Box-folder 59/19)
        - Tri-Boro Envelope Company (Box-folder 59/20)
        - Miscellaneous: Invoices (Box-folder 59/21)
        - Miscellaneous: Receipts (Box-folder 59/22)
        - Miscellaneous: (Box-folder 59/23)
          - Purchase orders
          - Shipping orders
          - Statements
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 59/24)
    - Inter-Office Business
      - Balance sheets (Box-folder 60/1)
      - Board of Directors and Stockholders
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 60/2)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 60/3)
      - Employment
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 60/4)
        - Employer Contribution Reports
        - Payment receipts [employees and services] (Box-folder 60/5)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 60/6)
      - Mailing/shipping (Box-folder 60/7)
        - C.O.D. senders's receipts: See Box 65
        - Customs Declaration forms
        - Insured mail receipts: see Box 65
        - Mail receipts: see Box 65
        - Post Office box payment receipts
        - Miscellaneous
      - Memos (Box-folder 60/8)
      - Petty cash vouchers: see Box 65 (Box-folder 60/9)
      - Telephone (Box-folder 60/10)
        - Monthly statements
        - Toll calls and telegrams statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Travel (Box-folder 60/11)
        - Automotive services receipts
        - Toll receipts: see Box 65
        - Traffic violations
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 60/12-13)
    - Mechanical Licenses & Royalties
      - Mechanical licenses
        - Contracts (Box-folder 61/1)
        - Correspondence (B-W) (Box-folder 61/2)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Royalties
        - Contracts (Box-folder 61/4)
        - Correspondence (B-W) (Box-folder 61/5)
        - Royalty statements: Corporate (Box-folder 61/6)
          - BMI (Broadcast Music, Inc.)
          - Beechwood Music
          - Burke & Van Heusen Music Publishers
          - Edward B. Marks Music Corp.
          - Harry Fox Agency
          - Jazz at Massey Hall
          - Leeds Music Corp.
          - Melotone Music
          - Music Publishers' Holding Corp.
          - Orpheus Music
          - Patricia Music Co. (Box-folder 61/6)
          - Rockaway Music Publishers
          - Vogue Productions Internationales Phonographiques
          - Walter Bishop Music Publishers
        - Royalty statements: Individuals (Box-folder 61/7)
          - Dennis, John
          - Dorough, Bob
          - Givens, Spaulding
          - Johnson, J.J.
          - La Porta, John
          - Levister, Alonzo
          - Macero, Teo
          - Mitchell, Bruce
          - Mobley, Hank
          - Most, Sam
          - Pettiford, Oscar
          - Scott, Hazel
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 61/8)
      - Professional Associations
        - American Federation of Musicians (AFM) (Box-folder 61/9)
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous [recording reports]
        - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) (Box-folder 61/10)
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous [recording reports]
        - American Society of Composer, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP) (Box-folder 61/11)
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous
        - BMI (Broadcast Music, Inc.) (Box-folder 61/12)
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous
        - National Academy of Arts and Sciences (NARAS) (Box-folder 61/13)
          - Correspondence
      - Promotional Material (Box-folder 61/14)
        - Debut Records Catalogs
        - Miscellaneous advertisements
      - Recording Projects
        - KENNY DORHAM: Kenny Dorham Quintet (Box-folder 61/15)
          - Contract
          - Miscellaneous
        - BABS GONZALES: Five Rocks and a Roll (Box-folder 61/16)
          - Correspondence
          - Invoices
          - Miscellaneous
        - THE GORDONS: The Gordons, M-110 and M-111 (Box-folder 61/17)
          - Contract
          - Miscellaneous
        - JAZZ AT MASSEY HALL: Jazz At Massey Hall, Vols. I and III -- Quintet, DLP-2 and DLP-4 (Box-folder 61/18-19)
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Expense statements
          - Invoices
          - Miscellaneous
        - JAZZ WORKSHOP: Jazz Workshop, Vol. I, DLP-5 (Box-folder 61/20)
          - Contract
          - Miscellaneous
        - JOHN LA PORTA: John La Porta Quintet (Box-folder 61/21)
          - Contracts
          - Promotional material
          - Miscellaneous
        - ALONZO LEVISTER: Manhattan Monodrama, DEB-125 (Box-folder 61/22)
          - Articles & clippings
          - Biographical sketch
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Invoices, receipts, etc.
          - Miscellaneous
        - TEO MACERO: Explorations, DLP-6 (Box-folder 62/1)
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Record production services [invoices, receipts, statements, etc.]
          - Record sales statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - CHARLES MINGUS: Charles Mingus Ninetette, Charles Mingus Quintet (Box-folder 62/2)
          - Contracts
          - Copyrights
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous
        - HAL MITCHELL: Hal Mitchell Four, M-104 (Box-folder 62/3)
          - Contract
          - Miscellaneous
        - ADA MOORE: Jazz Workshop, Vol. III: Ada Moore, DLP-12 and DLP-15 (Box-folder 62/4)
          - Biographical sketch
          - Correspondence
          - Miscellaneous
        - SAM MOST: Sam Most Quartet Plus Two, DLP-11 (Box-folder 62/5)
          - Biographical sketch
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Record production services [invoices, receipts, statements, etc.]
          - Record sales statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - CHARLIE "BIRD" PARKER: Bird On 52nd Street, JSW-501 (Box-folder 62/6)
          - Contract
          - Correspondence
          - Parker estate matters
          - Parker Memorial Fund
          - Miscellaneous
        - OSCAR PETTIFORD: The Oscar Pettiford Sextet (Box-folder 62/7)
          - Contract
          - Miscellaneous
        - BUD POWELL: Bud Powell Trio - Jazz At Massey Hall, Vol. II, DLP-3 (Box-folder 62/8)
          - Miscellaneous
        - MAX ROACH: Max Roach and His Sextette, M-105 and M-106; Max Roach Quartet, M-107 -M-109 and DLP-13 (Box-folder 62/9)
          - Contracts
          - Miscellaneous
        - HAZEL SCOTT: Hazel Scott, DLP-16 (Box-folder 62/10)
          - Biographical sketch
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Promotional material
          - Miscellaneous
        - STRINGS & KEYS: Strings & Keys, DLP-1 (Box-folder 62/11)
          - Contracts
          - Correspondence
          - Record production services
          - Miscellaneous
        - Discography: Lists of recording porjects (Box-folder 62/12)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 62/13)
      - Unfulfilled Mail Orders Requests: Corporate (Box-folder 62/14)
      - Unfulfilled Mail Orders Requests: Individuals (Box-folder 62/15)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 62/16)
  - Jazz Workshop, Inc.
    - Contracts (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Correspondence Received: Corporate (Box-folder 63/2)
      - A. Schroeder Music Corporation
        - Ames, Pearl
      - American Federation of Musicians
        - Ballard, Stanley
      - Bowling Green State University Libraries
        - Schurk, William L.
      - Bruhnke & Silver
        - Arons, Saul
      - Campbell, Connelly & Co.
        - Berry, Roy
      - City of New York Dept. of Real Estate
        - Levine, Morton
      - Cornell University: Willard Straight Hall
        - Atwell, Jeanne
        - Huggler, John
        - Moore, Edward J.: of Musicians' Local 132, Ithica, NY
      - The Evelyn Music Co., Ltd.
        - Sherriff, David
      - GEMA (Box-folder 63/2)
        - Urban, Heinz
      - H.M. Inspector of Taxes
        - Cropper, E.
        - White, G.W.
      - I.S. Dansk Grammofonpladeforlag
        - Knudsen, Karl Emil
      - Karpatkin & Karpatkin
        - Karpatkin, Marvin Moses
      - Mechanical-Copyright Protection Society Limited (Box-folder 63/2)
        - Skinner, H.N.
      - Orenstein, Arrow & Lourie
        - Silverman, Noel L.
      - Rank Productions Ltd.
        - Holland, D.F.
      - Sonoma State College (Box-folder 63/2)
        - Larolyi, A.F.
      - Warner Bros. Records, Inc.
        - Harman, Leo D.
    - Correspondence Received: Individuals (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Cohen, Elias I.
      - Crisp, John C.
      - Goldfield, Brian
      - Hurley, Catherine
      - Jackson, Gwendolyn S.
      - Keep, Linda
      - Mayo, Barry
      - Monea, Dominick A.
      - Tilemann, Barbl
      - Ungaro, Sue Graham
    - Correspondence Sent: Corporate (Box-folder 63/2)
      - Cornell University: Willard Straight Hall
      - Mingus, Judith A.
    - Correspondence Sent: Individuals (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Chance, William C.
      - Dumoulin, R.
      - January, Allan G.
      - Milner, L. [receipt for bass]
      - Soffer, Sheldon
    - General Services: Vender Sales and Services
      - Banking
        - Chase Manhattan Bank
          - Cancelled checks (Box-folder 63/4-5)
          - Correspondence (Box-folder 63/6)
          - Statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank (Box-folder 63/7)
          - Cancelled checks
          - Charges to account
          - Deposit slips
          - Statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 63/8)
      - Vender Sales and Related Services [miscellaneous] (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Inter-Office Business
      - Balance sheets (Box-folder 63/10)
      - Employee insurance (Box-folder 63/11)
        - Correspondence
        - Insurance policies
        - Miscellaneous
      - Employee payments [signed check stubs and voided blank checks] (Box-folder 63/12)
      - Receipt and release of lien forms (Box-folder 63/13)
      - Taxes: New York State and federal (Box-folder 63/14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Mechanical Licenses & Royalties
      - ABC-Paramount (Box-folder 64/1)
        - Contracts
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Ampex Corporation (Box-folder 64/2)
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box-folder 64/3)
        - Contracts
        - Correspondence
      - Royalty statements (Box-folder 64/3)
        - Miscellaneous
      - BMI (Broadcast Music, Inc.) (Box-folder 64/4)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Bethleham (Box-folder 64/5)
        - Royalty statements
      - Cadence Records, Inc. (Candid Records, Inc.) (Box-folder 64/6)
        - Contract
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Capitol Records, Inc. (Box-folder 64/7)
        - Royalty statement
      - Columbia Records (Box-folder 64/8)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Columbia Records of Canada Ltd. (Box-folder 64/9)
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Compo Records (Box-folder 64/10)
        - Contracts
        - Royalty statements
      - Decca Records Ltd. (Box-folder 64/11)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - E.M.I. Records (Box-folder 64/12)
        - Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous
      - Electrical & Musical Industries Ltd. (Box-folder 64/13)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Fantasy Records (Box-folder 64/14)
        - Correspondence
      - Royalty statements (Box-folder 64/14)
        - Miscellaneous
      - J. Herbert Orr Enterprises Inc. (Box-folder 64/15)
        - Contract
      - Liberty Records, Inc. (Box-folder 64/16)
        - Royalty statement
      - Mercury Record Corp. (Box-folder 64/17)
        - Contracts
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Motown Record Corp. (Box-folder 64/18)
        - Contracts
      - Nordisk Copyright Bureau (Box-folder 64/19)
        - Contract [unsigned]
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Philips' Phonographic Industries (Box-folder 64/20)
        - Contracts
        - Correspondence
      - Prestige Records, Inc. (Box-folder 64/21)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
      - Quality Records Ltd. (Box-folder 64/22)
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Radio Corporation of America, Record Division (RCA) (Box-folder 64/23)
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Sparton of Canada Ltd. (Box-folder 64/24)
        - Contracts
        - Correspondence
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - United Artists (Box-folder 64/25)
        - Royalty statements
        - Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous royalty statements (Box-folder 64/26)
    - Promotional Material (Box-folder 64/27)
      - Charles Mingus brochures
      - Concert announcements
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 64/28)
- Iconography (Box 67, Box 81, Box-folder 83/4-7)
  The Iconography series consists of photographs, artwork, and three dimensional items.
  Iconography series is arranged as follows:
  Photography, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Awards and award nominations, arranged chronologically by date.
  Artwork, arranged alphabetically by medium type (painting, record jacket layouts).
  Postcards, arranged alphabetically by subject or name.
  - Photographs
    - Charles Mingus alone (Box-folder 67/1)
      - Snapshots: various sizes (6)
    - Mrs. Charles Mingus, Susan Graham Mingus, portrait: 8 x 10 (2) (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Photo Negatives ... see also Box 77 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Photos of other musicians
      - Miles Davis (5) (Box-folder 67/5)
      - Eric Dolphy (1) (Box-folder 67/6)
      - Duke Ellington [and ...?] (1) (Box-folder 67/7)
      - Maynard Ferguson (1) (Box-folder 67/8)
      - Oscar Pettiford (5) (Box-folder 67/9)
      - Dannie Richmond (1) (Box-folder 67/10)
      - Max Roach (8) (Box-folder 67/11)
      - Artie Shaw (1) (Box-folder 67/12)
      - Horace Silver (2) (Box-folder 67/13)
      - Kai Winding (3) (Box-folder 67/14)
      - Unknown (3) (Box-folder 67/15)
    - Portraits: Mingus family & friends
      - 8 x 10 (4) (Box-folder 67/16)
      - Wallet size (8) (Box-folder 67/17)
    - Slides (76) (Box-folder 67/18)
    - Snapshots: Mingus family & friends (52) (Box-folder 67/19)
    - Miscellaneous photos (7) (Box-folder 67/20)
  - Awards and Award Nominations
    - National Academy of Recording Arts & Sciences (NARAS): Grammy Award nomination, Jan. 1973 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, New York: Hall of Fame Award, July 1976 (Box-folder 81/2)